- There. Done.
- All right.
Twelve minutes and 17 seconds.
Oh, pretty good, right?
(Sheldon:)That's 4.9 Penny Blossoms per hour.
(Sheldon:)Based on your cost of materials
and your wholesale selling price...
(Sheldon:)...you'll effectively be paying yourself
$5. 19 a day.
(Sheldon:)A day?
(Sheldon:)There are children in a sneaker factory
in Indonesia who out-earn you.
(Penny:)That just can't be right.
- You're questioning my math?
- No, sorry.
- Would you like me to show my work?
- God, no, no.
(Penny:)- Just please tell me what to do about it.
- All right.
(Sheldon:)Are you familiar with the development
that resulted from Honoré Blanc's...
(Sheldon:)...1778 use of interchangeable parts?
(Sheldon:)The assembly line, of course.
Okay, if I'm not allowed to be snide,
you're not allowed to be condescending.
(Sheldon:)That wasn't a part of our original agreement
and I do not agree to it now.